若我能开始改变
If I could begin to be
到你期望的一半
Half of what you think of me
我愿付出我的一切
I could do about anything
我甚至能学着去爱
I could even learn how to love
我看到你的举止
When I see the way you act
期盼着我的归来
Wondering when I'm coming back
我愿付出我的一切
I could do about anything
我甚至能学着去爱,如你
I could even learn how to love like you
爱,如你
Love like you
我总认为我非常卑微
I always thought I might be bad
现在深信不疑
Now I'm sure that it's true
因你如此完美
'cause I think you're so good
而我一点不如
And I'm nothing like you
你的举止,我都很欣赏
Look at you go, I just adore you
我希望知道
I wish that I knew
为什么认为我特殊
What makes you think I'm so special
若我能开始改变
If I could begin to do
如你一样的完美
Something that does right by you
我愿付出我的一切
I would do about anything
我甚至能学着去爱
I would even learn how to love
看到你关切的脸
When I see the way you look
长久分离的担忧
Shaken by how long it took
我愿付出我的一切
I could do about anything
我甚至能学着去爱,如你
I could even learn how to love like you
爱,如你
Love like you
爱我,如你
Love me like you